<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Moonlight Movement</title>
    <link>https://moonlightmovement.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Moonlight Movement</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://moonlightmovement.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DC Book Share Project</title>
      <link>https://moonlightmovement.org/blog/book_project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moonlightmovement.org/blog/book_project/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview Inaccurate airwaves are flooding government websites and broken media in Washington DC. Regular people are having trouble accessing accurate information on the government shutdown and how to fight back.
In honor of defending free press and National Banned Books week, the Moonlight Movement and allies are organizing the delivery of key anti-authoritarian books to little free libraries all around Washington DC. This organizing effort in partnership with book publishers, local groups, and more is aimed at educating residents of the nation&amp;rsquo;s capital on democratic backsliding, history, occupation, and resistance tactics as the attacks, abductions, and violations of the law by the current administration continue to escalate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moonlighting Examples</title>
      <link>https://moonlightmovement.org/blog/examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moonlightmovement.org/blog/examples/</guid>
      <description>Parallel Examples from other Nations </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vision</title>
      <link>https://moonlightmovement.org/blog/vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moonlightmovement.org/blog/vision/</guid>
      <description>4 year vision: Organize workers to use their skills to provide services to protect people from corporate greed and government overreach. Candidates 2025 We will be launching a slate of anti-authoritarian candidates for 2025-2026 at all levels of government inspired by a Zohran Mamdani-style smile and hustle politics with a gorgeous vision of the future. Immigrants, federal workers, and all the beautiful people the president is attacking will be at the heart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Moonlighting?</title>
      <link>https://moonlightmovement.org/blog/definition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moonlightmovement.org/blog/definition/</guid>
      <description>What are parallel institutions? What is moonlighting? Parallel institutions, or organizations that reflect back official institutions and services of government, have been instrumental across continents in preventing, resisting, and overturning authoritarianism and totalitarian rule. Unlike civil society institutions that are simply a formation of people with a shared interest, parallel institutions mirror state institutions or functions. Government institutions are formed with an obligation to perform a specific function or duty - a parallel institution partially replaces or fills in the function of the main institution that is eliminated, not performing, or being used for other use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQs</title>
      <link>https://moonlightmovement.org/faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moonlightmovement.org/faqs/</guid>
      <description>What is Project Moonshot?  Project Moonshot is a grassroots advocacy group dedicated to protecting democracy, combating car dependency, lowering energy costs, and ensuring the responsible implementation of AI. We bring together passionate individuals and organizations to drive meaningful policy change and create a more just, sustainable future.  What issues does Project Moonshot focus on?  We work across four key areas:  Protecting Democracy – Defending voting rights, fighting misinformation, and ensuring fair representation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://moonlightmovement.org/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moonlightmovement.org/page/about/</guid>
      <description>The Moonlight Movement is a growing workers movement building creative resistance to corporate power grabs and government corruption. Moonlight organizes accessible resistance based on the skills workers and people already have to provide services and care that should be basic protected freedoms.
We don’t need another non-profit with a new twist, we are building a transformative framework of constructive organizing that is as much about keeping people safe as it is about building a new paradigm.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
