<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Blist Multilingual Theme</title>
    <link>https://moonlightmovement.github.io/en/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Blist Multilingual Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://moonlightmovement.github.io/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>4 Year Vision</title>
      <link>https://moonlightmovement.github.io/en/blog/vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moonlightmovement.github.io/en/blog/vision/</guid>
      <description>The constructive forms of resistance we build will create accessible pathways for millions of people to use skills they already have to take care of their neighbors and fight corruption to stem and reverse the highest autocratic tide in generations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moonlighting Examples</title>
      <link>https://moonlightmovement.github.io/en/blog/explained/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moonlightmovement.github.io/en/blog/explained/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Moonlighting?</title>
      <link>https://moonlightmovement.github.io/en/blog/definition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://moonlightmovement.github.io/en/blog/definition/</guid>
      <description>Definition of a parallel institution from the International Center on Nonviolent Cooperation: “Alternative [or parallel] institution-building is understood broadly as the process undertaken by organized civilians to establish new practices and organizations that are parallel to and aim to challenge dominant socio-economic, cultural, and political structures viewed as unjust and oppressive. Some examples include alternative schools; health clinics; publishing houses… proto-political and governing institutions, and community service organizations”.
Source</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
